yourhealthadvice.com 2012-12-20

# Privacy Policy « Health Articles | Alternative Health | Healthy Times Newspaper Archives

**Personal Information:**

Your personal information is important to us. All personal information you share your education, such as name, postal address, phone number, email address or other personal information will be stored securely and encrypted so that third party can not capture, read or use this information when it is transmitted Teaching online between your computer and transferred to service providers to help provide competitive offerings. We may also share personal information with third parties to manage the business or ancillary services, and as otherwise permitted or required by law. Privacy Policy always comply with applicable federal and state laws.

**Links to Other Websites:**

Our site contains links to other sites and http;//www.yourhealthadvice.com/ is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third party sites. You should always read the privacy statements of Web sites related to their privacy policies may differ substantially from ours. Do note that when you click one of these links will be redirected to another site.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are small text files stored on the hard drive of your computer while the browser is running. Online Training does not use cookies to track, collect or store your personal information. However, we may use cookies to make it easier for older users to fill one of our insurance quote forms. If you do not accept cookies, you can easily change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies from being stored and still visit the online education.

**Tracking Pixels:**

Some pages on Education Online may contain electronic images known as tracking pixels or single-pixel GIFs. These points may collect non-personally identifiable information, such as cookie numbers of visitors, time and date of page view, visitor referring URL and a description of the pages they visit. The information collected using these pixels does not identify individual users. Online Education is committed to the security of your personal and financial information. Our servers and data processing are in a secure environment protecting your account information to access a third party.
